We're going to start with the eye on the seventh day.
我们将从第七天开始观察眼睛。
We are in embryology.
我们正在研究胚胎学。
And it's funny because I think, well, it's funny, it almost looks like an eye.
这很有趣，因为我想，嗯，这很有趣，它几乎就像一只眼睛。
Especially on the eighth day, it's a bit like an eye.
尤其是第八天，它有点像一只眼睛。
But what's quite interesting is, what appears on the eighth day?
但有趣的是，第八天出现了什么？
A small cavity appears, which we call the amniotic cavity.
出现了一个小腔，我们称之为羊膜腔。
This amniotic cavity is fundamental.
这个羊膜腔是至关重要的。
The eye, it comes from the brain.
眼睛来自大脑。
in fact from the diencephalon, or more specifically, it is an expansion of the third
实际上来自间脑，或者更具体地说，它是第三脑室的延伸。
ventricle.
脑室。
But at some point, the neural system will receive primitive amniotic fluid.
但在某个时刻，神经系统将接收原始羊水。
primitive.
原始羊水。
This primitive amniotic fluid will form what we call CSF. So
这种原始羊水将形成我们所说的脑脊液。所以
your first
你的第一个
CSF is amniotic fluid. It will enclose the fluid in the neural tube,
脑脊液是羊水。它将把液体封闭在神经管中，
neural tube, and then poof,
然后砰的一声，
growth, we will see, of this tube.
生长，我们将看到，这个管子的生长。
which will open towards space, towards the front,
它将向空间，向前开放，
which will form these primitive vesicles.
它将形成这些原始囊泡。
But in fact, it's a bubble
但实际上，它是一个气泡
that inflates.
它膨胀了。
Of air.
从空气中。
But where is the remnant of this amniotic cavity?
但是这个羊膜腔的遗迹在哪里呢？
It's what we call the pocket of bones.
这就是我们所说的骨袋。
We call that zone B.
我们称之为B区。
An individual.
一个人。
And inside, you have...
在里面，你有……
cerebrospinal fluid.
脑脊液。
In the compartments,
在隔间里，
in lateral ventricles, etc.
在侧脑室等。
But outside of you,
但在你之外，
you have,
你有，
in embryology,
在胚胎学中，
what we call another fluid
我们称之为另一种液体
which is amniotic fluid.
那就是羊水。
This fluid that is inside here
这种在这里面的液体
and which is outside here,
和在这里外面的液体，
it's the same fluid.
是同一种液体。
The eye, which is here, is a membrane, constantly seeking
眼睛，在这里，它是一个膜，不断地寻求平衡B区。
to balance zone B.
不断地寻求平衡B区。
Zone B means that if you look at me, we will consider that my axis, my
B区，这意味着如果你看着我，我们会认为我的轴线，我的
physical body,
身体，
from my central line, would be my zone A.
从我的中线开始，将是我的A区。
And around me, I have what we call this amniotic cavity that starts here.
在我周围，我有我们所说的羊膜腔，
amniotic cavity that starts here.
它从这里开始。
Look where it starts, eighth day, that's when we enter the mucosa.
看它从哪里开始，第八天，那是我们进入黏膜的时候。
There is a loss of central fluid, an exudate,
中央液体会流失，渗出液，
which will form a small cavity.
会形成一个小腔。
And when this small cavity appears, I will have my ectoderm that will
当这个小腔出现时，我的外胚层就会
be put in place,
就位，
what is called at this stage the epiblast.
在这个阶段我们称之为外胚层。
But that means that already here, it's the whole subtle structure.
但这已经意味着，这里是所有精微的结构。
that will form the eye, that will form the brain.
它将形成眼睛，形成大脑。
And at the same time, this amniotic cavity.
同时，这个羊膜腔。
Then, this amniotic cavity, look what it will become.
然后，这个羊膜腔，看看它会变成什么。
A huge pocket that surrounded you for nine
一个巨大的囊，在九个月里包围着你，
months,
个月，
but which is no longer liquid now,
但现在它不再是液态的，
but which is vaporous around you.
而是你周围的蒸汽状。
So around us, we have this space,
所以我们周围有这个空间，
we have this protection, and which must be in fact...
我们有这种保护，它实际上必须是……
in balance with your
与你自己的内部液体保持平衡。有时，
own internal fluid. Sometimes,
它处于不平衡状态。有时，
it's advanced. There are people, they are
它向前倾斜。有些人，他们是
in rotation.
旋转的。
Any accident, any whiplash, is an imbalance
任何事故，任何鞭打，都是这个层面的不平衡。
at that level. So, the eye,
这个层面的不平衡。所以，眼睛，
it's a balance
是你的液体深度，你的神经系统，
fluid, of your nervous system,
你的液体，你的神经系统，
which is the CSF,
也就是脑脊液，
which is fundamental,
这是基础，
and also the space
以及你周围的空间
that is around you.
你周围的空间。
That's why just observing the position of the eyes,
这就是为什么仅仅观察眼睛的位置，
just observing how the eye will position itself in space,
仅仅观察眼睛如何在空间中定位，
it shows you how you are interfering with what is around you.
它就向你展示了你如何与周围的事物相互作用。
We already see if you have this balance and you will learn to observe the eyes,
我们已经可以看到你是否有这种平衡，你将学会观察眼睛，
we all have a different eye, we all have an eye that is a little forward
我们都有不同的眼睛，我们都有一个稍微向前突出的眼睛。
because it is also related to the architecture of your brain,
因为它也与你的大脑结构有关，
the best balance for you.
最适合你的平衡。
mediastinum, we seek
纵膈，我们寻求
to have a
获得一种
horizontality in relation
水平性相对于
to a verticality. I have a
垂直性。我有一个
horizontality in relation to my verticality
相对于我的垂直性的水平性
in a mediastinal listening
在纵膈听诊中
which is in a left
它在左侧。
laterality. So
所以
my whole body here goes to the left
我身体的整体在这里向左
and I'm looking for myself here.
而我在这里寻找自己。
And so I'm looking for my horizontality
所以我寻找我的水平性
in relation to my system
相对于我的消化系统，
digestive, in relation to my peritoneal
相对于我的腹膜系统。
peritoneal system.
腹膜。
always seeking this balance.
一直寻找这种平衡。
So the manifestation of how the eye will position itself,
所以眼睛如何定位的表现，
that's the best answer you can get.
这只是你能得到的最佳反应。
That's why it's very important to observe the eyes after treatment.
这就是为什么治疗后观察眼睛非常重要。
If you do a treatment and the person gets up,
如果你进行治疗，然后病人站起来，
and you see that their eyes are...
你看到他们的眼睛是...
It's not over.
还没结束。
Do you understand what I mean?
你明白我的意思吗？
This space here, but this amniotic cavity,
这个空间，这个羊膜腔，
it has something around you, like that, you see, that's there.
它周围有东西，就像这样，你看到吗，它在那里。
it's very important to be able to restore this balance.
重新建立这种平衡非常重要。
The eye will be the expression of your imbalance in your zone B.
眼睛将是你B区失衡的表达。
And zone B is that.
B区就是这个。
You see, this space around the embryo, like that.
你看，胚胎周围的这个空间，就像这样。
Well, this space, in my practice, in my perception,
嗯，这个空间，在我的实践中，在我的感知中，
is still there.
仍然存在。
Not in liquid form,
不是以液态形式，
because water can be found in different states.
因为水可以以不同的状态存在。
It can be found on an ice-like plane,
它可以以冰状平面存在，
a vapor-like,
蒸汽状，
there is still this space around
周围仍然有这个空间
and we feel it.
我们能感觉到。
I can enter here, at some point, we will enter intimacy.
我可以在这里进入，在某个时刻，我们将进入亲密关系。
I want to put it here.
我想放在这里。
And each one will have this space more or less large.
每个人都会有或大或小的空间。
With radiations
伴随着辐射
quite important because the heart
相当重要，因为心脏
emits a magnetic radiation,
会发出磁辐射，
it has been calculated, even verified,
这已经被计算过，甚至验证过，
up to 4, 5, 6 meters
最远可达4、5、6米
around you.
在你周围。
Also in relation to that.
也与此相关。
It is important to understand, first of all, this relationship that exists between this amniotic cavity,
重要的是要理解，首先，羊膜腔、眼睛和
amniotic cavity, the eye, and
眼睛，以及
the entire ventricular system.
整个脑室系统之间的关系。
Because this is a ventricular system, and I tell you, the eye is an expansion
因为这是一个脑室系统，我告诉你们，眼睛是
of the third ventricle.
第三脑室的扩张。
But it already expands before the closure of the anterior neuropore, just before this closure.
但它在神经孔前部闭合之前就已经扩张了，就在闭合之前。
And we will see that there will be a whole genetic implication.
我们将看到这将涉及整个遗传学。
very interesting, with co-localizations on
非常有趣，在
different impact zones,
不同的影响区域
such as the same information on the hepatopancreatic level, for example,
有共定位，例如在肝胰腺方面有相同的信息，
with the same coding genes, cardiac and thyroid.
具有相同的编码基因、心脏基因和甲状腺基因。
Diabetes will express itself on the eye.
糖尿病会在眼睛上表现出来。
The heart will express itself on the eye.
心脏会在眼睛上表现出来。
Organized level by the neural crest that we will review a little in the study of laterality,
由脐嵴组织化的水平，我们将在侧向性研究中再次看到，
of the organization of the median axis through this primitive median line.
通过这条原始中线来组织中轴。